brief about the product if you have any
doubt any question feel to please ask
again so let me just briefly tell you
about the product uh this is a first of
It kind product which we have launched
for health customers uh in India this
product is designed uh uh which has a
unique features which are there uh which
which primarily takes care of uh the the
basic need of any customer uh this
product is designed keeping one
phenomena in feature in mind that there
are various type of customers in the
market and everyone requires uh a
product which is Suits him and has to be
very very uh unique or or or or
personalized in nature uh we have
designed this product which is purely
customizable you can design customize as
per your need uh and it is backed by
artificial intelligence also uh more
importantly uh it has got many unique
featur which are industry first uh which
is there not not there in the industry
as a whole uh we have introduced a new
uh add-on cover which is there in this
product which is in finite gear it tells
it says that uh in the lifetime of the
policy uh one claim of uh unlimited
amount can be taken by any customer uh
which is is not there unheard of in the
industry itself uh not only this many
other features like uh cumulative bonus
which is also addon cover which can be
bought as per the need of the customer
which says that every year 100% bonus
will be given to the customer uh and
this can go up to unlimited times
currently in the market there are addon
benefits like cumulative bonus uh which
goes up to a certain times uh in the
lifetime of the uh policy but in our
policy we have said it can go up to
Unlimited time we have reset benefit
which is already there also we have
introduced a unique feature which is a
jump start uh this gives a flexibility
to to cover uh any pre-existing customer
for which is there with any customer and
it will give a unique feature which says
that you need not to wait for 3 years to
start coverage of those uh PDS which are
there which is pre-existing disease you
have uh there uh the PD will get covered
from 31st day that is again a unique
proposition for our customers and again
I'm saying that it is very much
customizable you can personalize as per
your requirement no need of buying or
mandatory covers are there uh it is
completely to the flexibility of the
customers uh we have just launch this
product and the response which we are
getting on this product is really
amazing so thank
[Music]
inite